[Kingdom Episode 30 Translation by Kewl0210]
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
飛信(ひしん)隊を率いる信(しん)の活躍で―
After going on the offensive thanks to the Feixin Unit, led by Xin,
趙(ちょう)との戦いが 攻勢に転じると―
王騎(おうき)は すかさず 蒙武(もうぶ)に全軍を預け
一気に 本陣の陥落をねらった
Wang Qi lost no time in giving Meng Wu custody over the entire army
with the goal of felling the enemy headquarters in one mighty blow.
（録嗚未(ろくおみ)）第１軍 出撃だ！
First Army, sortie!
（隆国(りゅうこく)）第２軍 出陣！
Second Army, go!
（鱗坊(りんぼう)）第３軍 出るぞ！
Third Army, let's go!
（同金(どうきん)）第５軍 突撃せよ！
Fifth Army, charge!
（万極(まんごく)）秦国(しんこく)軍のヤツらも…
The State of Qin guys are also...
（李白(りはく)）戦略を変えてきたか！
They changed their battle strategy?!
（干央(かんおう)）第４軍 行くぞー！
Fourth Army, charge!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）だが 信たちが
あと１歩で突入というとき
But when Xin's group was a step away from invading the headquarters,
the battle suddenly underwent a massive change!
突如として
戦況に大きな変化が訪れた
（信）な… なに！
Wh-What?!
（信）どういうことだ？
What's going on?
趙のヤツらが ひいていく…
The Zhao guys...
are retreating?
What's going on here?
（貂(てん)）何なんだ？
趙の本陣がある山が静かになったぞ
The mountain where the Zhao headquarters is located has gone quiet?
（蒙毅(もうき)）趙の中央軍が…
The Zhao central army!
Hey, hey! What's with this all of a sudden?!
（貂）おいおい なんで いきなり…
あれじゃ 本陣が丸裸じゃん
They're leaving the headquarters completely exposed, aren't they?!
（蒙毅）ひょっとして…
（李牧(りぼく)）ほ～う…
Perhaps...
（李牧）
早くも趙軍は雲隠れするようですね
It looks like the Zhao Army has already disappeared, hasn't it?
（カイネ）李牧さま
Lord Li Mu...
There are visitors here already.
先客がいますよ
（李牧）えっ？
Li Mu
（李牧）やあ どうも
李牧と―
Hey there!
I am Li Mu, and this is my outstandingly beautiful guard, Kaine!
Kaine
美人すぎる護衛の
カイネです
（カイネ）ハァ…
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
時は紀元前 春秋戦国時代の秦国
The setting is before the common era,
the State of Qin during the Spring and Autumn Warring States Period.
名もなき少年 信は
若き王 政(せい)と出会い―
The nameless boy Xin met with the young King Zheng,
武功を上げて
ついに 百人隊の将にまでなった
distinguished himself in war, and finally become a Hundred-Man General.
そんな中 突然 隣国の趙が攻め入り
未曽有の危機が訪れる
Among those events, the neighboring State of Zhao suddenly invaded,
presenting an unprecedented crisis.
総大将 王騎は
いかなる戦いを仕掛けるのか
What kind of war will Supreme Commander Wang Qi wage?
そして
信は いかなる成長を遂げるのか
And what kind of growth will Xin achieve?
Presented by Anime-Destiny
itsumo yori hayaku kietetta hoshi zora ni
いつもより早く消えてった星空に
In a starry sky that disappeared faster than it ever has
Translation
kewl0210
kusanariatta deai wa
重なり合った出会いは
the many piled up meetings we've had
Editing
jagman1x3
ore wo nomikonde iku
俺を呑み込んでいく
swallow me.
kono yume wa kudakenai
この夢は砕けない
This dream cannot be broken.
Timing
rtrs
sabitsukaseta kyoufushin
錆びつかせた恐怖心
Among this rusted fear in my heart
yuragu fuan no naka de
揺らぐ不安の中で
and the anxiety that makes me waver
Typesetting
kewl0210
ame wo saegiru shinjitsu
雨を遮る信実
is a truth that interrupts the rain.
dare ni mo ubaeyashinai
誰にも奪えやしない
No one can take it away,
Karaoke
kewl0210
FZeroWing
onaji keshiki ni hisonda puraido
同じ景色にひそんだプライド
our pride that lurks in the same landscape.
Encode
max80
itsuka kitto kanau ima mo mieru kibou fortitude
いつかきっと叶う 今も見える希望 fortitude
The fortuitous desire I have will definitely come true one day.
yowasa wo sute wa shinai
弱さを捨てはしない
We won't throw away our weaknesses,
oretachi no kienai shiin
俺達の消えないシーン
those are scenes that won't disappear.
furenzokusen no youni hashiru kibou unbreakable heart
不連続線の様に走る希望 unbreakable heart
My desire in my unbreakable heart runs like a discontinuous line.
I knew at the start that there's no end.
QC
Mistral[sA]
I've made up my mind, right now it's the time to take the first step.
Distro
kokus
Kittie
prefix-
Now's the only time.
～♪
Disaster
Lower the Zhao flag!
（兵士）趙の旗を下ろせ！
（兵士）我らの旗を掲げろ！
Raise our flag!
（昂(こう)）本陣 取ったんだよね？
てことは―
We... took the headquarters, didn't we?
So does that mean...
Ang
勝ったの？
（田永(でんえい)）アホ
we won?
Idiot.
（昂）…てえ
（田永）ヤツらは
本陣をよそへ移しやがったんだ
They moved the damn headquarters someplace else
戦力を保つためにな
To preserve their war capability.
（尾平(びへい)）
じゃ また追っかけんのかな？
Then... do we chase after them again?
当ったり前(めえ)だ
Of course we do!
ここまで来て 取り逃がすか
We ain't gonna turn back after coming this far!
…たく
軍長のヤツらは何やってんだ？
Geez. What the hell is that combat commander thinking?
モタついてっと
向こうが立て直しちまうぞ
If we don't hurry, they're gonna reform over there!
（隆国）
ヤツらは 戦場を山あいに移したか
So they moved the battlefield to between the mountains, did they?
（同金）これでは
どこにいるのか分からぬな
So now we don't know where they are, huh?
（隆国）
いや 山が切り立っているからこそ
No. Because of how large the mountains are,
軍を配置できる場所は絞られる
上から眺めれば 一目瞭然だ
there is only one very narrow place where an army can be stationed.
If we looked from above, we could find them in one glance.
（隆国）ヤツらも
当然 それを前提に考えているはず
And of course, they would have thought of that before they made their move.
（干央）追うべきと思うか？ 隆国
（隆国）俺に聞くな 干央
Do you think we should follow them, Long Guo?
Don't ask me, Gan Yang.
昨夜の軍議で殿が申されたであろう
You heard what Lord said in last night's war council.
（王騎）趙本陣の山を制圧しても
本陣自体は後ろへ逃げるでしょう
Even if the Zhao headquarters takes control of the mountain,
the headquarters itself will run behind it.
それを追うかどうかは状況しだい
Whether we follow them or not will depend on the situation at that time.
決定は 現場の将に委ねます
The right to decide will go to the general at the actual location.
つまり 蒙武 あなたにです
In other words, you, Meng Wu.
A battle between mountains brings with it the danger of being difficult to coordinate with allies.
（王騎）山あいでの戦いは―
味方と連携が取りづらく
危険を伴います
くれぐれも冷静に
Do take the utmost care to keep a cool head.
無論 追う
Of course, we follow.
Yes, sir!
（隆国）念のため 確認を
Just as a precaution, we should confirm our next action.
昨夜 王騎将軍が話された約束を
覚えておいででしょうな？
You remember the promise General Wang Qi spoke of last night, yes?
However, if you choose to pursue and attack them, promise me one thing.
ただし 追い打ちをかけるのなら
ひとつだけ約束を
（王騎）範囲です
Your range!
追い打ちをかけていいのは 趙の
本陣だった山が見える範囲までです
The only time you should be attacking the routed enemy
is when you can still see the mountain where Zhao's headquarters was previously.
これを決して破らぬように
Please be sure not to go against these instructions...
分かっている
I understand!
（騰(とう)）動きだしましたな 殿
（王騎）ンフッ…
They seem to have started moving, Lord.
あ～らあら せっかく来たのに―
Hey, now. I finally get here,
皆さん
山の向こう側へ消えちゃいましたね
and everybody disappears behind the mountains.
It seems that the only thing I'll be able to see
これでは
ここから見えるのは もう―
秦軍の本陣の背中だけですねえ
is the back of the Qin Army headquarters.
まあ それだけでも せっせと
歩いてきた甲斐(かい)はありますか
Well, perhaps it was still worth the trek all the way out here.
He-Hey! I said not to ignore me!
（貂）
お… おい！ 無視すんなっての
ンンッ… 何者なんだよ？ お前ら
勝手に上がってきやがって！
Who the hell even are you?!
Don't just waltz up here without asking!
とりあえず ２人とも 剣を置け！
And anyway, put away your swords, you two!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）秦軍の本陣では
移動に向けての準備が完了していた
The Qin Army headquarters had completed preparations for relocation.
趙本陣のあった山は完全に制圧され
そこまでの間にも 敵軍の影はない
They took complete control over the mountain that the Zhao headquarters had occupied previously.
And in the process of doing so, they saw neither hide nor hair of the enemy.
秦軍の本陣移動は容易な状況である
The relocation of the Qin Army headquarters was an easy task.
しかし ここで
これまで動きの早かった王騎が―
But here, Wang Qi, who had previously been very quick to act, was uncharacteristically silent.
珍しく沈黙した
えも言われぬ違和感
There was an indescribable uneasiness...
それが
王騎をこの場に押しとどめていた
That was because Wang Qi had stopped at this location.
This Zhao Army retreat...
（王騎）趙軍の この撤退
練りに練られた策の気配を
感じますねえ
I sense a well polished plan...
そうなると
４日間の趙軍の負け方が―
If that's the case, that would mean the way the Zhao Army lost in the first four days was intentional,
わざとということになりますが
それは まず ありえない
but that is impossible to begin with.
かすかに奇妙な においがしますよ
It certainly has a suspicious smell to it...
騰…
（騰）はっ！
Teng.
Yes, sir?
向こうの軍師は
趙荘(ちょうそう)のほかに誰かいましたか？
Besides Zhao Zhuang, are there any other strategists on their side?
いえ いないはずですが
No. There should not be.
ンフフッ… まあいいでしょう
本陣を動かしますよ 騰
Well, fine, then.
Let's move the headquarters, Teng.
Yes, sir.
（王騎）いずれにせよ
In any event,
あぶり出しに
行かねばなりませんからねえ
we'll merely need to uncover any plans they have...
一向に姿を現さぬ あちらの大将を
And the one that has yet to show himself is their Great General...!
（李牧）秦軍の本陣も動きましたよ
（貂）えっ？
It looks like the Qin Army's headquarters is on the move, too.
They're moving the headquarters to the other side of the mountain so they can commanded more easily.
（李牧）指揮が執りやすいように
向こうの山へ本陣を移すのです
分かってるよ そんなこと…
バカにすんな
Yeah, we know!
We're not idiots!
しかし これで
グッと近づくことになりますよ
But now they're really getting close to each other...
両軍の大将同士が
The Great Generals of the two armies...!
さあ 移動しましょう 皆さん
ここにいても戦は見えません
Okay, everyone. Shall we get moving ourselves?
We won't be able to see the fight from here.
（貂）ちょっと待て！
Hold on a second!
なんで いきなり
お前が仕切ってるんだよ？
Why are you in charge all of a sudden?!
（李牧）いいじゃないですか
お互い 野次馬(やじうま)同士 こういうのは
It's not a problem, is it?
We're fellow curious onlookers.
Doing it in a group like this is more exciting, isn't it?
大勢のほうが盛り上がりますよ
（貂）なっ…
馬車に
同乗させていただけませんか？
Would you do us the favor of letting us join you on your carriage?
我々の馬は ちょっと遠いので
Our horses are pretty far away, you see.
ンンッ…
ずうずうしいこと言いやがって
You sure are presuming a lot!
そう簡単に…
（李牧）実は この先にも―
Do you think we're just gonna...
You see, there's another mountain castle ruin a bit past here that we can watch from.
観戦に うってつけの
山城跡があるんですよ
なんだと？
What?!
いいでしょう
（貂）えっ？
All right, then.
ただし
ひとつだけ お願いがあります
But I have one thing to ask in return.
And that is?
（李牧）何ですか？
（蒙毅）あなたたちの剣を―
Would you let us hold onto your swords?
こちらに預けていただけませんか？
（カイネ）ンッ…
こんな所で
素性の知れぬ方と同乗するのは―
You could understand that we might be afraid to ride together with people
それくらい怖いですよ
察してください
whose background we know nothing of.
Please understand.
All right. We'll let you hold onto them.
分かりました　預けましょう
（カイネ）ええっ！
ありがとうございます
（カイネ）私のは預けませんよ…
Thank you very much.
I'm not giving you mine!
Okay, let's get going.
早速 たちましょう　日が暮れます
The sun is setting.
（カイネ）李牧さま！
Lord Li Mu!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）秦軍の新たな本陣の
設営が進む中 王騎は―
While the construction of the Qin Army's new headquarters was still in progress,
Wang Qi put foot soldiers on standby at the foot of the far side of the mountain in preparation for any changes.
歩兵を 山の裏手の麓に待機させ
事態の変化に備えた
一方 蒙武軍には 隆国が加わり
敵本陣までを先導
Meanwhile, the Meng Wu Army, along with Long Guo, were guided to the enemy headquarters.
The other armies advanced, maintaining their formation with the Meng Wu Army as the center.
そのほかの軍も 配置は そのままに
蒙武軍を中心として進軍していたが
But as of now, they have yet to confirm an encounter with the Zhao Army.
いまだ
趙軍との遭遇は認められなかった
（王騎）龐煖(ほうけん)に関して何か報告は？
（兵士）いえ
Has there been any report regarding Pang Nuan?
No. All military commanders have reported no sign of him.
各軍長ともに
気配なしとのことでした
ンフッ…
随分 じらしますねえ 龐煖
You do like to tease, Pang Nuan...
９年前の あのことで
警戒が強くなっているのですか？
Did you become more vigilant after those events 9 years ago?
ンフフフッ… しかし あなたも
隠れているだけでは―
But if all you do is hide,
not even you will ever get my head.
私の首は狙えませんよ
（尾平）このままいけば―
If we keep this up, we might actually get back to the village pretty soon.
意外と早く 村に帰れそうだな
Yeah. And then we'll all be heroes to the whole village!
（有義(ゆうぎ)）
ああ そしたら みんな 村の英雄だ
将軍を討ち取ったっつったら
村のヤツら どんな顔するだろうな
Man, I wonder what kinds of faces the villagers will make when they hear we took down a general!
Long You
Bang
Qu Hai
Tian Yong
俺 帰ったら
東美(とうび)ちゃんと結婚するんだ
When I get back... I'm gonna get married to Dong Mei.
（有義）いや 誰も聞いてないし
Nobody's listening to you, bud.
大丈夫？ 別に
約束したわけでもないんでしょう？
Are you sure? You didn't get engaged or anything like that, right?
するっつったら するんだ！
（笑い声）
I said I am, and I meant it!
（慶(けい)）おう その意気で頑張れ
Yeah, that's the spirit. Go for it.
到(とう)のヤツは“年上のお前より
先には結婚できねえ”って―
We can't have Dao get married before you, what with you being the older one.
ずっと 女 待たせてんだからな
（尾到(びとう)）ちょ… ちょっと 慶さん
So he's gonna keep his woman waiting forever.
H-Hey, Qing!
なに？ そうだったのか？ 到
What?! Is that true, Dao?!
あ～ すまねえ！
もうちょっと待ってくれや
I'm sorry. Just wait a little longer, okay?!
（脇次(きょうじ)）
澤(たく)さんとこのガキは５つだったか？
Your kid is five, right?
（澤圭(たくけい)）いや ６つになりました
No, six now.
なんだよ うちと同じか　男？
（澤圭）男です
What? Same as mine.
A boy?
Yes, a boy.
（脇次）ハハッ！ やっぱ 男だよな
Yeah, thought so.
（兵士）
バカ 女の子のほうが かわいいぞ
You idiot. Girls are the cute ones.
（兵士）いや 男だろう
（兵士）バカ 女だって
No, boys.
Girls, you idiot!
竜川(りゅうせん)とこの赤ん坊は
やっぱ でけえの？
I'll bet Long Chuan's new kid is huge, huh?
（竜川）いや 普通…
Well... it's normal.
おう 軍議 やっと終わったぜ
Hey. The war council's finally over.
うん？ どうした？
Huh? What's up?
（羌瘣(きょうかい)）別に
Nothing.
ただ…
（信）えっ？
It's just...
（羌瘣）
みんな 帰る場所があるんだな
Everyone has a home to return to.
お前…
（羌瘣）気にするな
You-
Don't concern yourself.
深い意味はない
持っているものは人それぞれだ
I didn't mean anything significant by that.
What one has varies from person to person.
私は私で 生きる目標は持っている
I have my own reason for living...
（信）敵討ちは大事だ
Revenge is important.
だがな 羌瘣
それで終わりじゃねえぞ
But you know, Qiang Lei, it doesn't end with that.
敵討ちが済んだら―
After you get revenge, you'll still be alive and have a future.
生きてるお前には
その先があるんだ
ホントは お前だって
そのことに気づいてるんだろう？
Even you realized that, don't you?
はぁ？
（信）“はぁ？”…じゃねえよ！
What do you mean "huh"?!
お前は 敵討ち放っぽって
参戦したんだ　自分の意思でな
You put aside revenge to participate in this war! And by your own will.
てことは―
That means you've got one.
お前は ちゃんと持ってんだよ
飛信隊っていう立派な帰る場所をな
A great home to return to, the Feixin Unit!
勝手に決めつけるな
Don't decide that for me.
来い　軍議の内容 みんなに話す
C'mon. I'm gonna tell everyone what happened in the war council.
Or do you dislike this place?
それとも
ここが気に食わねえのか？
別に…
（信）じゃ 決まりだ
Not particularly.
Then that decides it!
（羌瘣）気に食わないことはない
There's nothing I dislike.
いや むしろ―
No, far from it...
居心地は悪くない
I'm actually quite comfortable.
だから きっと―
That's why I'm a little perplexed...
少し戸惑っているんだ
な… 何だ？
Wh-What is...
この気配は…
this presence?!
Hey, who's over there?!
おい 誰だ？ そこにいるのは
趙兵か？ そこで何してる？
A Zhao soldier?
What're you doing over there?!
どこの部隊の者だ？
（兵士）止まれ！ 所属を答えろ
What unit are you with?
Stop! Tell us what group you're attached to!
（尾到）うん？ どうかしたか？ 信
What's up, Xin?
信！
Xin?!
この気配は… まさか蚩尤(しゆう)？
This presence...
Could it be... a Chi You?!
No, that's not it...
いや 違う
似ているが どこか違う
It's similar, but something is different...
これは ひょっとして…
Could this be...?
（兵士）て… 敵襲ーっ！
E-Enemy attack!
敵襲だー！
It's an enemy attack...!
やっぱり そうか…
I knew it...!
おい どこの部隊がやられた？
敵の数は？
Hey, which unit got attacked?
How many enemies are there?!
（兵士）あの丘の向こうだ！
It's going on over that hill!
The lookouts were apparently wiped out so fast that they didn't even have time to signal!
見張りの部隊が
合図をする間もなく全滅したらしい
なんだと！
What?!
敵軍がいない？
There's no enemy army?
あそこの守備の一隊は全滅してるが
敵は どこ行った？
That defensive unit was totally wiped out. But where'd the enemy go?
ほかの部隊が集まったから
逃げたのか？
Did they run away after the other units gathered?
（羌瘣）いや まだいる
No. He's still here...
この騒ぎで気配を見失ったが
まだ この野営地の中にいる…
I lost track of his presence in all this commotion,
but he's still somewhere on this campsite.
But where?!
どこだ？
敵襲のドラ 間違いじゃねえのか？
Maybe it was a false signal?
（渕(えん)）ちょっと様子見てくる
（尾到）全然 静かじゃねえか
I'll take a look at their condition.
It's totally quiet, don't you think?
（三和(さんか)）な… 何だ？ てめえ
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
（三和たち）ウワッ！
アア… そんな…
No way...
三和たちが…
Shan He and the others are...
ウソだろう…
This isn't real, right?
何なんだよ こいつは！
What the hell is that guy...?!
（崇原(すうげん)）逃げろ みんなー！
Everyone, run!
助けに行かねば… 助けに…
I have to go save them...
I have to...
I'm a Vice General! What am I doing?
副将のくせに何をしている…
みんなが…
Everyone...
みんなが死んでいく…
Everyone's dying!
信どの…
Lord Xin!
（信）さっきまで
一緒にバカ騒ぎしてたんだ
Until a minute ago, everyone was fooling around and having a great time together.
This can't be happening, right?!
（竜有(りゅうゆう)）何なんだ？ こいつ
What the hell is this guy...?
（尾到）見てるだけで…
Just from looking at him...
（尾平）寒気が止まらねえ…
I can't stop shivering...!
I am a calamity from the heavens.
（龐煖）我は 天の災い
ここにいるお前たちは ただ…
You people simply...
（兵士たち）ウワーッ！
had no luck.
運がなかっただけだ
（兵士たち）ウワーッ！
み… みんな 逃げろ！
E-Everyone, run!
（有義たち）ウワッ！
有義！
You Yi!
助けてくれー！
Help us!
ウワッ！
みんな 四方へ逃げろ… 四方へ…
Everyone... Run in every direction.
Just get away from him...
声が出ぬ… 脚が動かぬ…
I can't speak...
My legs won't move...
信どの… 信どの…
Lord Xin... Lord Xin...
このままでは
飛信隊が死んでしまう…
At this rate, the whole Feixin Unit will die...!
What're you guys doing?!
（田有(でんゆう)）何やってんだ お前ら！
立て！
（澤圭）尾平さん 立って！
Stand up!
Please stand, Mr. Wei Ping!
アアッ… ダメだ 立てねえ…
（尾到）兄貴 早く！
It's no good. I can't stand up!
Big Brother, quick!
（尾平）に… 逃げろ ２人とも！
R-Run, you two!
（田有･中鉄(ちゅうてつ)）アア…
（尾平）信…
（信）ンンッ…
Xin!
てめえ… 何してくれてんだよ？
You bastard... what did you do...?
ただで死ねると思うなよ…
Don't think death will be enough to make up for this!
（去亥(きょがい)）やる気だ…
He's gonna fight.
信なら当たり前だ
Well, it's Xin, after all.
だが…
But...
（崇原）
やめろ 隊長！ かなう相手ではない
Stop, Captain!
You're no match for that guy!
オラッ！
す… すげえ 信のヤツ
I-Incredible...
Xin, he's...
ウワッ！
（渕）あっ！
立て
Stand.
ナメやがって…
Looking down on me...
し… 信…
X-Xin...
（信）心配すんな お前ら
Don't worry, you guys.
The one who's gonna die... is him!
死ぬのは こいつだ
なに！
What?!
He dodged Qiang Lei's sword with that giant body?!
羌瘣の剣を
あの巨体で かわしやがった
ほう…
Oh. It seems it was you who called me.
どうやら
我を呼んだのは お前のようだな
What the hell is going on?!
一体 どういうことだ？
（龐煖）子供だが
You may be a child...
命をもらうぞ
but I'll be taking your life.
I don't know what that bullshit you're spouting is...
（信）なに ワケの分かんねえこと
言ってんだ？ お前は
…つうか
そもそも お前は 一体 何なんだ？
And who the fuck are you, anyhow?!
２万を超える俺たちの野営地に―
You plunged into our campsite of over 20,000 soldiers alone, and started killing...
１人で飛び込んできて
殺しまくりやがって
Are you a Zhao soldier?
趙兵なのか？ だとしたら
１人で夜襲なんて 何がしたい？
Then what are you trying to achieve with this night attack?!
No, wait...
いや 待てよ　こいつ
“自分を呼んだのは羌瘣”って…
This guy said it was Qiang Lei who called him...
（羌瘣）お前みたいなヤツを
呼んだ覚えはないぞ
I don't remember calling anyone like you.
（龐煖）お前の意思ではなく
存在が呼んだのだ
It was not by your will. It was your existence that called me.
我が内に潜む荒ぶる神は―
The wild god that dwells within me cannot allow for the existence of any other strong beings.
他の兵(つわもの)の存在を一切 許さぬ
（羌瘣）貴様は何者だ？
Who the hell are you?
我… 武神 龐煖なり
I... am the War God, Pang Nuan.
（信）
武神？ それって 前に羌瘣が…
War God?
The thing Qiang Lei was talking about before...
龐煖？ 今 あの男 龐煖って…
Pang Nuan?
Did that man say he was Pang Nuan?!
龐煖？
Pang Nuan?
（魯延(ろえん)）龐煖じゃと？
Did he say Pang Nuan?
龐煖とは 確か―
Isn't Pang Nuan...
趙軍の総大将の名前だぞ！
the name of the Zhao Army Supreme Commander?
関係ねえ！
It doesn't matter!
武神だろうが何だろうが関係ねえ！
I don't care if you're a War God or whatever! It doesn't matter!
This guy killed Shan He, Zie Ci, Fa Jian, and a ton of others!
こいつは 三和や脇次
筏建(ばつけん)たち みんなをやりやがった！
絶対 許さねえ！
There's no way in hell I'll forgive him!
敵(かたき)を討つぞ 羌瘣！
We're going to avenge them, Qiang Lei!
Of course.
当然だ
挟み込んだ　２人がかりでやる気か
They're attacking in a pincer formation.
They're gonna take him on together?
くそ！ 俺らも…
（崇原）やめろ　足手まといになる
Damn. Then let's go too...
No. We'll only get in their way.
我々にできる援護は
ここに とどまって見守ることだ
All we can do to back them up is stay here and watch over them.
（去亥）でも２人で勝てんのかよ？
相手はバケモノだぞ！
But can they win with just the two of them?!
Their opponent is a monster!
いや 信と羌瘣なら―
No. This is Xin and Qiang Lei. I know they'll find a way...
きっと…
ウワッ！ ウッ…
（尾平たち）信ーっ！
Xin!
あっ！
（尾平）ウソだろう！
You're kidding me, right? Even Qiang Lei...
羌瘣まで…
（羌瘣）
トーンタンタン トーンタンタン
トーンタンタン
Ton... Tantan...
michi wa tsuzuku yume wo oimotome
路は続く　夢を追い求め
The path goes on, chasing after a dream.
nozomu saki ni kimi no ashita wa aru no?
望む先に　君の明日はあるの？
Will your tomorrow be at the place my hopes lead?
kizutsuite kokoro mo mada kawaku nara
傷ついて　心もまだ渇くなら
If I get hurt and my heart is still thirsty,
koko e kite nando demo utau kara
ここへ来て何度でも歌うから
I'll come here and sing as many times as it takes.
owari naki tatakai no naka de
終わりなき戦いの中で
In this endless battle
kimi wa tsuyoku kawaru
君は強く変わる
You change to become stronger.
kono sora wo kirisaita ikazuchi wa kimi
この空を切り裂いた　雷は君
The lightning that cut apart this sky is you.
osore wo koete tachimukau hikari no ya hashiridasu
恐れを超えて立ち向かう　光の矢　走りだす
The arrow of light that overcomes fear faces forward and shoots forth.
tsukamu sadame shinjitsuzukeru no...
掴む　運命　信じ続けるの…
I'll grab onto the destiny I've always believed in...
～♪
Preview
（信）ここで逃げてるようじゃ
天下の大将軍なんて 夢のまた夢だ
If I run away here...
becoming the greatest general under the heavens will be just a dream within a dream!
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）狙うは一瞬の隙
無敵の男に 百の刃(やいば)を突き立てる
His target is a single moment of opportunity.
A hundred blades are thrust at the invincible man.
The Power of a Group
End
次回 “集の力”
Next time,